Ending
Hello, this is Yuna Shibata.
Today I came to Tokyo Dome by myself.
I'm still on my way.
The title of my sibling's song is "One Man's Heaven", so
I came to Tokyo Dome by myself
I'm on my way home from work
I'd like to go and have a bit of fun!
Thank you very much for watching.
I've come indoors.
I heard there is a batting center here.
I've never been to this batting center before.
I'm looking forward to it.
Ta-da!
I'm here at Spodori!
I'm off to the batting center.
I'm not used to being alone.
I'm not confident about my batting,
I'll do my best.
I'll go. My turn has come.
What should I do? Oh, no.
We're here.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
Go for it!
Oh, I wish I could win this.
I hit it, I hit it, I hit it!
That's good, right?
Oh, it's good, isn't it? It's good. It's good.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's good, right? It's good, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Are we done?
The end?
Did you see that?
I think we did pretty well.
I don't know. I didn't do it.Eh, I don't know. I haven't been able to do it.
But I think I've made it to the end after all these years, so...
Next time, I'd like to pitch.
I can do that.
Thank you for watching.
He's so cute.
Is it on?
Ha-ha-ha.
I've already forgotten how to throw the ball that Satosaki taught me.
I should have done a little youtube review.
I remember how to do 123, but I don't know what 123 was.
Wait, left? Right?
1, 1, 2, 3, haha, I don't know
Oh, 123, okay, okay, left, right, left, right, left. Okay, okay.
And elbows straight. Oh, okay, okay, okay, I remember. I remember.
Go for it!
Wait, first of all, I'm afraid of the ball flying at me.
First of all...
Wait, first of all, I'm afraid the ball will come flying at me
Here I go!
Wait, I'm nervous to raise my hand
Oh, no, no, no!
Wait, I have to throw this quickly!
Here I go.
50 kilos, that's not even close!
Come on.
Fifty-four.
Okay, OK.
Oh, oh, oh, this is no good. The one you shouldn't do in the uterine formula.
OK, OK.
I can't reach it. Not at all.
Oh, this one's no good, either.
Next time I come to Tokyo Dome, I'll make one more stop here.
I'd like to practice by myself.I'd like to practice on my own.
One more time. I'll come back next time.
I can see it.
Oh, no.
This flag here...
It's supposed to be for the live show.
When my friend and I came to Tokyo Dome to see the game.
He told me it was Nogizaka.
It's so clear.
There are no clouds.
The Ferris wheel and the view.
I love the view.
You can see the Tokyo Dome and the Ferris wheel from this angle.
This is Gate 21 today.
Last time it was 20.
Oh, yes, I've been coming to Tokyo Dome
I've been coming here a lot this season.
I came to Tokyo Dome to watch a baseball game by myself.
But what is the most exciting moment for me when I come to a baseball game by myself?
It's when I get to my seat.
I looked for an aisle called "Namban Aisle".
If it's here, when I'm going down the stairs
When I'm going down the stairs, wondering where my seat is.
I always get nervous.
So far, so good.
We're at baggage claim.
I'm going to go through.
I'm used to this door, I'm used to it.
I'm in, inside.
I'd like to take a picture today so as not to disturb others.
Ta-da! Okamoto.
Gate 21, 11 way.
Gate 21, 11 and 22.
Last time I was here, I was here with my grandfather.
21, 12, oh, I guess it's around here.
Row 26, 290. 26 rows.Row 26, row 290.26.
I'm in.
Eh, wait a minute. It was the other way around, the other way around, the other way around.
Oh, it's still on, on, on, on, on, on, on.
Here it is. 16 rows, 11 aisles, 2...oh, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
It's here. Look, it's here.
What should I do?
Oh, no, it's not good. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Alone in Tokyo Dome with my camera.
I've seen the seats and I want to go to the merchandise store.
Usually when I get to my seat, well, I just get up to buy food once.
I don't move much from my seat,
But it's still early today, so I'd like to go.
Ta-da!
Here we are!
Giants!
Now let's go in!
There's one for dogs.
Maybe I'll buy one for Coco.
Hey, this is the towel section.
Well, the manager asked me to...
I was asked by the manager to bring a lot of towels.
The goods I was asked to buy are...
A towel and a key chain of Mr. Kikkawa, who is it?
But there is a possibility that they are sold out.
Oh!
Then! He was originally a member of the Lotte team!
Oh, there he is, there he is!
I saw him, I saw him!
And a key chain, as requested.
This is what he asked me to do as an errand boy.
I did this the other day.
Then Kikkawa came out.
What should I do? I'll do something.
I'll put on my aurora bracelet today.
Which one do you like?Which one do you like?
Oh, this one.
I'll get this one.
Okay, we're gonna re-enter.
The GIANCE players, as a group, are throwing suicide signing goals into the stands.
Here come the players.
Wow.
That's cool.
I love the rhombus.
Oh, they're all throwing!
Okamoto, Cotton.
Maybe he won't come here
Here, here, here
Wow, here it comes
Go, go, go, go, go.
Wow.
Here it is.
He didn't come?
He didn't come here.
Too bad.
It's starting!
Speaking of which...
You know what?
The Tokyo Dome
Lotte game at Tokyo Dome
After work.
I came alone.
My seat was...
A little more to the right over there.
A little closer to Gaia.
I came alone.
I'll open it.
Let's open the package!
I wonder who'll be good.I don't know who I'd like.
This is like 20 different types, 20 different people.
Maybe Director Hara.
Who is it?
Then!
Oh! What? Wait!
Wow! Director Hara!
Well, I'll wear this on my wrist today to cheer for him.
This and this are the goods for Mr. Kikkawa that the manager requested for his errand.
Now, here are the goods requested by Mr. Kikkawa for his errands.
[Adult Mamire girl in the future, Mamire Katsudo]
I'm going to put my heart and soul into it.
Everybody's orange!
Thank you for watching.
I think these are on their way.
Wait.
I don't always get these.
You're definitely getting one today.
You couldn't?
It was a little too close. Too bad. I couldn't get it today either.
I come to Tokyo Dome a lot after work,
There are a lot of people like that, and when I'm around businessmen, it's great to hear them complaining about their companies. It's fresh and fun, so I keep coming back and forth.
It must be nice.
I think that's what I like about ballparks in Tokyo.
It's easy to go there after work.
I used to go to Marin from Tokyo Station on the Keio Line,
I have been there,
But Tokyo Dome is just in time for me even if I finish late at night,
So I come here.
Let's eat.
Oh, Ishikawa is still on board.
He's playing for Lotte now. He's very active, isn't he? Ishikawa.
What shall we eat?
It's fun.
I can't believe how empty it is when the game starts.
Really. Yes, it is.Really. Yes, I did.
I just got dressed.
Potato salad. Mokko mokko~.
Matsuda's thick double meat burger melt.
This looks delicious, doesn't it?
In coming to Tokyo Dome by myself
I watched a lot of vlogs of people watching baseball games alone on YouTube.
So I went to the front of the venue after having studied the vlogs.
I was not sure what looked so good....
Oh!
It's a hit.
Look!
Oh, yeah!
So cute! Can I take a selfie?
Yes, cheese! Thank you! Bye-bye!
It's done! I got it! We did it! I got it! I got it! I did it!
I was able to take a picture by myself! So cute!
Last time I came here alone, it wasn't so good.
I was nervous! I was nervous, but I'm glad it turned out okay!
Five beef cutlets in one!
Five in one?
I got it! Beef cutlet!
This is so much fun!
It's fun to get dressed and go home!
I'll need to bring some goodies when I come here on a regular basis!
Can I go to Gyukatsu?
Yes, you can!
Bon appétit!
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
Hot! Hot!
Five!
Yes, thank you.
YouTube?
Good luck.
Thank you.Thank you!
(clapping) clapping
This is...
If you look from the stairs on the first floor there, to the left...
There's some class 12 stuff there.
I'd like to open it.
I'd love to see you, Tsubaki.
You're going to perform at Jingu, aren't you?
I'm looking forward to it soon.
I haven't had a chance to meet Tsubaki.
I'd like to meet her someday.
As for the random key chains...
It's been on my make-up pouch since last year.
Oh, this is the one from the cup.
Oh, wow!
That's a "Se de, Se de, Se de"!
Oh, wait, you're right.
I have Yakult.
Look at this.
This one and this one.
Wow, I think this is pretty good.
So cute!
Ta-da!
It's the Yakult game today.
So cute!
I want to collect these.
They're so cute!
Next time I go to Jingu.
I'll take a look.
Wow!
Yay!
Yeah!
Gush! Gush! Gush!
Gush!GUSH!
Woo!
Congratulations!
Taro Nakata's
Gash of ishishine!
Ooh!
Once!
Whoo!
Ohhhhhh! Elijah Kim
The game is over. Thank you very much.
I came here today after work,
I enjoyed myself even though I was alone, and I would like to go back again by myself,
But I still felt a little lonely,
I would like to come again with someone.
I wore a T-shirt and had a lot of fun.
I will go again.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating.
See you soon.
[ED].